<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="toast">This code doesn\'t exist</string>
    <string name="locaties">Locations</string>
    <string name="voer_code_in">Enter code</string>

    <string name="openingText">Welcome! \n\n\n
        Before we can embark ourselves into this adventure it is necessary to be informed about what are the possibilities
        in the Esteling during your visit. U might have heard about the new elements the Esteling has added, these elements
        form a new way of experiencing the attractions. To make this experience complete, we need you! You will be able to endulge
        yourself in this new adventure that will be available at each and every attraction the Esteling offers. Each attraction has its own
        storyline. But, these storylines are hidden. This is where you will partake. Are you able to collect every story? Down below u will find a short instruction. \n\n\n
        - Choose the attraction you would like to visit \n
        - Fill in the code on ur phone as soon as you enter the queue \n
        - Search for the lit-up lights on the inside of each room \n
        - Aim your flashlight at the construction beneath the light \n
        - Press the flashlight button on your phone to activate a code \n
        - If the light fades you have unlocked a new part of the story
        - Collect all the parts of the attraction and experience the complete story \n
        Have fun!!
    </string>

    <string name="helpDialog">
        - Choose the attraction you would like to visit \n
        - Fill in the code on ur phone as soon as you enter the queue \n
        - Search for the lit-up lights on the inside of each room \n
        - Aim your flashlight at the construction beneath the light \n
        - Press the flashlight button on your phone to activate a code \n
        - If the light fades you have unlocked a new part of the story \n
        - Collect all the parts of the attraction and experience the complete story \n
    </string>

    <string name="helpTitel">How it works:</string>
    <string name="roger">UNDERSTOOD</string>
</resources>